Hi. Remember the plan? Well, throw that plan out the window and let it rot outside because plans
have changed. The edge of sleep is available right now. Not a joke. Not a drill. Not a mistake.
But it's available right now through the link in the description below on Prime Video. I couldn't
say that before for reasons that I still do not fully understand. But it's out now, so I'm not
going to wait any longer because no one else is waiting for this. Or I mean, everyone else is
waiting for this because all the marketing is still set to go up on the 18th. And it is currently
the 15th, which means we have a few days where we are on our own, but the challenge is still there.
So go outside, grab the plan, dust it off, and bring it back inside because we still have a job to do.
Apparently. So I don't think it's going to make a difference though. I really don't. Even though
we're on our own, that's never really stopped us before. And so I think there's still plenty of
time and plenty of opportunity to make the challenge happen. If you need a reminder,
the challenge was to get it into the top 10. There's a couple of shows that are probably up there
right now. We need to dethrone them. I don't even know what they are. Whatever they are right now.
Okay, what do we got? Okay, in TV shows, you got Lord of the Rings, Rens of Power, Citadel,
Diana, Pulsa King, the legend of Vox, Machinima, lioness, killer cakes,
Reacher, the boys, Fallout, and Judy Justice. So all we got to do is beat the ever-living snot
out of that literally judge Judy. We got to beat the snot out of Judge Judy. All right, sorry.
Miss Judy Shindlin, Mrs. Judy Shindlin? Sorry, Judge Judy. You got to go.
We'll give it back in a little bit, but you got to go. All right, it's sorry. That's just the way it
is. So that's who that's our target. That's our target. Yep, Judge Judy is our target.
So I think we can beat her. I think we can beat her. And you know, all these other shows,
they haven't had a new season in a bit. And all of it doesn't matter. We just need to get into the
top 10. And if we go higher than that, that's great. But we are on our own. So we got to make
do with whatever we can. It's available right now, but you do need a prime subscription to watch it.
The benefit free trials. If you don't have it, you can get a free trial for it. Just be sure to
cancel it if I shouldn't say that. But you know, I'm going to say it anyway. If you get a free trial,
just be sure if you can't afford the rest of it, cancel it before it's done. And if you're outside
of the US, you won't be able to watch it without a VPN. Now I don't know if that counts detrimentally
towards the views, but I don't really care because it's more about people watching the show. But if
you're outside the US, there probably is a VPN that'll work for you depending on what country you're
in. I don't know which specific one. I don't have a VPN sponsor right now. And even if I did,
I wouldn't know if they would be the right call for where you are. But if you want to watch it,
VPNs work. And there are free trials for those as well. So we're going to do whatever the
fuck it takes to make this happen because circumstances be what they may. And the plan is still the plan.
Even though it's been battered and dusted off, the plan is still here. And the challenge still needs
to be met. The entire future of whatever the hell I want to do rides on this. And I know they're
going to meet the damn challenge, even if we got to do it on our own, which probably was all we
got to do in the first place. I don't think it was malicious. I don't think that there's any
conspiracy about this. I think they just didn't expect you guys to find it that soon, even though
I kind of told you to do that. But you know, it's not a bad thing. No one made a mistake here. We
had a meeting earlier today that was like, well, this has never happened before. And I'm like,
yeah, well, it should have been obvious. But here we are. So they're still all going to do all the
actual traditional marketing push on the 18th, which means that we have a few days where they're
not expecting it. So we can catch them by surprise. Whoever they are, we're going to catch them by
surprise judge duty, we're going to catch her by surprise. And then fall out that that really so
long ago, and then the boys, and then reach her and killer cakes. What's killer cakes? I've never
even heard of that. Bakers with terrifying skills, competing the most frightening challenges,
working with top horror effects artists to create cakes. So disgusting and realistic,
they're nightmarish. Don't pay attention to that. I don't care if that was captivating. We got to
put that off. All right, put that to the side and get sleeping. Get your edge on, get to sleep,
and then watch head to sleep. Link is in the description. Spread the word about it because
there is going to be absolutely no marketing about this for the next few days. And I don't
know if that's going to hurt the momentum of everything. So we kind of got to push it as hard
as we can right now. Take off the handcuffs. Unchain thyself. Release the beast within.
Think of imagine I said something inspirational here. Imagine I said something incredibly inspirational.
Imagine that I was saying something that spoke directly to your soul that penetrated all these
shells of insecurity and incompetence and tapped into the real you that was there.
Imagine these words are really resonating with you. They remind you of someone,
maybe a parental figure that you never got close enough to. But now you're reminded of them.
My words are tapping into unseen memories. You know, Ratatouille, my words are doing the strawberry
cheese mixture. I don't care if in real life that wouldn't actually happen or even taste that good.
This speech that I'm giving you right now is so goddamn inspirational. You feel like you could
rip down a mountain. That would have been something cool that I could say. But I didn't say it.
This is just a hypothetical of what if I did that. So imagine that. Put yourself in that space.
And real hard. Sleep real good and watch the show. Link is in the description.
Okay. That's it. I know you're wasting time here. You could be sleep.
Sleep engine. You could be sleaging. Let's get our sleeve, John. Don't ever quote me ever. Fuck.